What a question I'm getting today!
I solicited questions in advance on my instagram.
That's the official instagram of Dai Mamoru, isn't it?
Yes, and we got a whopping 700...
Seven hundred and eighty-two.
Wow.
Thank you very much.
So I'd like to answer this question, although my time is limited.
Daima-san, Mirei-chan, please tell me what you like about each other.
Isn't it delicious?
What do you like about each other?
What do we like about each other...
Yes...
No, I don't.
Yes, we do.
First of all, there's your feet.
No, I'm your uncle. Feet.
The princess's feet look delicious.
Triangle's people are probably delicious. Princess's feet.
Oh, yeah, maybe.
But what I like most about her is... what I find amazing...
I think it's when she doesn't have to show her entire age range.
Hime puts what she wants to do first and foremost.
But she also cares about the people she gets along with.
I think that's the point where we can get along with each other without giving out at all.
I answered seriously. I'm too embarrassed to look at the other side.
The little ones get along well with each other all the time, don't they?
Yes, we're like the same age.
I'm in trouble for doing too much for Noya-chan right now, aren't I?
Let's think about it for a minute.
Can I have 30 minutes of your time?
I'm so worried.
I'm torn.
Hmm... Yeah.
You're that bothered?Why do you even bother?
You're going to do it.
You're that worried?
But I'm glad you're the oldest in the group.
Hmmm...
But we don't have a leader.
So it's not like there's a leader.
I can see what's going on around me.
I can see what's going on around me, so I can say, "This girl needs to do this.
I mean, there are a lot of times when I can just leave things up to the group.
Especially if it's a member who's been doing it for years.
Sometimes they can do everything.
You have to make sure that it's done right.
I'll let her do it because it's for her.
I'm like a mother.
She's like a mother.
I am a mother.
She notices if someone is having problems.
I think that's great.
And I think that if Mayasa wasn't the best.
I think if you weren't the best, you might have been a leader.
I think that's part of it.
I'm glad.
But there's probably a little sister-kissing going on there.
I think that's what sister-kissing does well.
That's good. You're answering to the stiff-armed stiff-guy.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Embarrassing.
Yeah, it's embarrassing.
Let's segue for a second.
Oh, you're gonna segue?
I think I'll segue.
I'll get used to it.
Looks good.
How do we eat it?
What's the first thing you two do when you wake up in the morning?What is the first thing you two do when you wake up in the morning?
Ooh.
Something more herbal.
I brush my teeth, too.
We're the same.
Brush my teeth and eat breakfast.
Brush my teeth and drink water.
I can eat anything I want in the morning.
Curry would be nice, but...
I can't eat much in the morning.
Oh, really?
Hotels do a good job with buffets, but...
Yeah.
I feel like I'm getting ready.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Other mornings, I don't even wake up.
I'll just do Grace and Protein.
Africa Nyan
I know, right?
Is it good?
Yum! So tasty!
And the spicy green peppers make it so delicious!
Do you lose the green peppers?
Green peppers!
Like the green peppers?
Green peppercorns! Bri-tou!
Next! Next!
Let's go!
You want to try?
Let me memorize a few things first!
Six!
I'm six!
And on and on!
Fall is almost here. Is there anything you would like to do in the fall?Fall will be here in a little while, is there anything you want to do in the fall?
I surprisingly like going to see maple trees!
I like nature more than I thought I would!
Surprisingly!
Really?
I like it more than I thought I would!
It's great!
I was on a trip the other day.
I was on a trip the other day and I found a hand bucket.
I was so excited!
I like nature and activities more than I thought I would!
Ah~~
And it's a great time of year to be outside!
I'm dramatic!
I didn't even see the "Pre-Pre-Pre" show in the summer.
I jumped in the river!
Yeah!
I didn't get to go much with my dad.
But the river's a little cooler now.
It's a little cold.
Oh, did he say what he wanted to do?
What?
Is there a lot of things you want to do?
Oxymoron fall, appetite.
Sports?
Yes, words.
Something special to do in the summer.
Oh, my God!
I'm scared! Is there anything special you want to do in the fall?
I mean, I can read all year round.
Oh, I want matsutake mushrooms!
Matsutake mushrooms!
Rice with mushrooms!
Mushroom rice!
You can eat mushrooms in spring too.You can eat mushrooms in the spring, too.
I've been into mushroom hot pot since spring this year.
It's delicious!
I eat mushroom hot pot all the time.
Even if it's not in the fall.
Japan is amazing!
Isn't Tokyo amazing?
Tokyo eats hamburgers for dinner!
Yes!
You can even eat rice in season if you feel like it.
You lose the feeling, you know, the specialness.
Yes!
No, no, no!
Oh, so Tanabata is the autumn of art.
Oh! What's up with that lately?
Japan is surprisingly...
I see it all the time on Instagram.
Dripping with paints and stuff.
Ah! Oh! I get it!
I want to go to that!
I want to go there!
Wanna go to that one?
I want to go with Kaho, him, and the three of us.
I wanna go!
We've been talking about it.
But me and Kaho, we're both a little overweight.
Well, let's look for a place and make a plan.
There are places like Shimokita and Shinjuku.
I want to try that.
I know! It's nice, isn't it?
I also want to do pottery.
Oh, I want to do pottery!
I want to make chocolates.
I want to go to a place where you can get sake as it is.
I saw it on Instagram.
Wow!Amazing!!!
All insta-stocked.
Stock up on insta.
I'd love to go to that one.
I want to make it an art fall.
Yeah!
I think so.
Okay, feel it.
Thank you for watching.
If you could switch places with each other for one day, what would you do?
What? What's that?
Don't you like carving?
I like both hobbies.
Like anime.
I like the collision part.
So, I kind of want to live.
Just for a day?
You carve it in one day?
Carve it in a day? Carve it in what?
The one-signature thing.
The one that looks like this.
Oh, but, you know, everyone sees it in one day.
What do you mean?
What do you mean, all in one day?
Random Samurai.
I'm just trying to get the nuance of it.
I get it. I get it. It's fine.
I'm just a random person.
I'm just a random person, or I'm going to go home and put my wallet on the table.
I'm a good one, right?
Yum!
Yum! Yum!
It's so good!
It's got some kind of blue in it.
Isn't it good with blue?Blue and tasty?
Yum!
I think this is...
Oh, wait, it's really good with blue.
I woke up after the blue stuff settled down.
I woke up.
I'm finally awake.
I'm finally awake, now
Blue and...
There are many people here.
I woke up at 12 o'clock, right?
I lost my watch to Mirechan?
I'm going to Korea.
That's nice.
I can go, too.
Mire-chan has a lot of friends.
I won't bother you.
I've met some of Mire-chan's friends.
Mire-chan's
I'm waiting for you with my used friends.
To all of Pekay
All of you at Pekay Company.
They're all great friends.
The people at Pecai are pretty calm.
They're very nice.
They're very calm.
But they're a little tense.
A lot of my friends are...
There are a lot of people who are a little bit crazy.
I'd like to interact with them a lot.
I'd like to meet a lot of them.
I'd like to go to Korea and travel there.
I really feel that Mire-chan is a princess, whether she's a shrimp or a private person.
Mire-chan is a princess both in her private life and as an Ebi.
I thinkBecause I think
They'll raise you like their own grandchildren.
I mean, they're cute, with their pictures and everything, but they're gonna know.
It's like...
I don't care too much about it. I just want to skip it.
Like, "Don't do it.
I'd like him to do it.
We've got something for you.
What is it?
How do I get a shy boyfriend to say he loves me?
You're cute.
What should I do?
I'm just trying to get my shy boyfriend to like me.
But, you know, it's not your fault if he doesn't do it.
But, you know, it's better than being told I like you.
I'd rather do it with a bamboo...
Isn't it precious?
Maybe it's precious.
I think...
I'd like to see a 23-year-old kid perform live.
I could do it more often.
I mean, maybe once a month.
Assuming he's doing gigs every day.
I think it would be more appealing to the fans if you did it once a month.
I think it's more likely to stick with the fans.
Personally, I think
That's why
To make people who don't usually say they like you
To get people who don't usually say they like you to say they like you
I'll try to do the same thing.
I'll do the same.
Suddenly they don't say they like me
I wonder why they don't tell me they like me
I'll make him feel it.
I'll make you wonder.That's what they want you to think.
I don't think she's a bargaining chip.
Personally, I don't think so.
What do you think?
It's a little different.
I don't know.
I feel like a liar.
Hmm.
Like what?
This time of year, the floor.
Is that it?
A little too long ago?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah! Something that says I'm only doing it for that person.
Yeah.
Like, "We don't cook, so I'm going to cook for you.
We don't cook.
But we're not cooking anything because that person isn't really cooking.
If the person who's making the food is the one making it, then I can only assume they're skipping out.
Huh? I don't know what to do.
I want to do something special.
Like, my hair isn't curly, so I'm going to try curling it.
Curl it.
You're gonna curl it.
Make her say how pretty it is.
Oh, you like it?
You like it?
Big whoop.
That's disgusting.
I don't like it.
I don't want to be called that.
Don't make me say it anymore.
Don't make me say it anymore?
Oh, that's exactly what you need to do.Oh, that's exactly what you need to do with this.
Ah.
Let me ask you something.
What do you think of me? Don't make me say any more.
Isn't that more embarrassing, Yuka?
Yes, absolutely.
Absolutely.
Yuka, that song is embarrassing.
Why not? It's a great song.
Why?
Why not?
It's good.
You're gonna have to. What are you gonna do now?
I'm telling you, you can't beat the touch of a finger.
It's that strong.
You're the one who can say, "What are we going to do now?
On the contrary.
It's not "kora".
That's why I think you're mentally strong.
No, I don't think it's not that.
I think I'm a little more mature at 23 or so.
I don't swing around like that.
Like a 23-year-old.
You definitely say that.
You're not good at it?
Oh!
Coffee from Cateuse's?
Cachouz.
No, not this one, the cider.
Wow!
I'll have the Cachouz coffee.
I'll have the cider version today.
Oh, I see.
I'll get it for you.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
So, even your father can do this?
No problem.
Oh!
Wow!
You're a bold find!
Bold!
Big!
Color?
Chill Sauce
I love this cider!
It's delicious...the way it makes you feel!
Yum!
Wow!
We're running out of time, aren't we?
Yeah, I know.
I think it's time for the ending.
Yes, ma'am.
We're going to continue eating through this.
But we still have over 700 questions.
There's over 700 questions.
That's not even close.
Not even close.
I'm looking forward to the next one.
Yes, that's right.
The last one was the honey makkori that I was talking about earlier.
We had a size-up version of the honey makkori I was talking about earlier.
Thank you very much.
Looks delicious.
Let's finish with a toast, shall we?
Cheers!
Sweet!
Yum!Yum!
Subscribe
Highly Recommended
Comments
Like
Please do something, anything at all!
Please!
That would be so helpful!
Oh, but the sweetness of the honey was so great and sudden it was beyond.
It's so good!
Can I taste the honey?
Yum!